We've made it to Venecia!
Hang on, we're going in!
Mista, you have to get out of the car!
Journal!
Your body!
Oh no, it's freezing!
I know I don't need to
tell you this, Vista.
But getting to the you-know-what
is our first priority here.
Securing it will cement our victory.
The disc is in there!
The vast amount of water will
slow down the freezing in the car,
so there's no better time to go!
I'll be okay. Just get moving.
Fine, have it your way.
Your definition of
victory needs some work.
Beating Ice Boy into
the ground and getting
the hell out of Dodge
with the disc in hand?
that's how it's done.
You won't get away!
Don't be shy now.
Take a dip, mister.
See, I'm willing to wager.
My ice migrates faster than you can
doggie paddle to the other side!
Damn it!
I guess I shouldn't have driven
the car into here after all!
This bastard's ice attacks!
They're unbeatable!
It's almost like you've been knocked down.
I'm not able to run away.
I'm not able to walk away.
But I'm not able to get away.
The goals of the world are born.
There's no hope to be?
We will continue to fight.
Fighting gold!
out of it while you still
have the chance so you're
trying to use those vines as
ropes are you as if i let you
it's no use if i want these
vines to make it all the way
across to the banks i'm going
to need some warmer temperatures
this sub-zero cold is too
extreme for anything other than
tundra grass now who said anything
about getting the vines to
the bank.
Grass is all I need.
It's just what the doctor ordered.
But I need more, and more, and more.
Unless you want to fight the
big one, grow me some grass.
Grow like your life
depends on it, Giorno.
I got you now.
Too bad you couldn't get
enough of the stuff to
make it to land.
Nice going there, Giorno.
It finally froze.
Disaster avoided.
That asshole!
He made the frozen grass into
a freakin' ski! Crafty dick!
Hey, who said you could use a snowboard?
I'd be crazy to think this lunatic
would let me off the hook that easy.
Stop this guy, white ice!
Switch off the deep breeze now!
No, the ice is...
Melting!
Mister!
The realm of ice is the realm of stasis.
Cold's piercing embrace
settles all into inertia.
Ice halts everything!
Hence the reason my stand, white
ice, is the paragon of perfection.
It can still the fury of the sea,
and soon you'll feel its power!
Pull yourself up already! Mista!
Mista, go for the grass
that's down in the water!
That stuff you used as a board! Quick!
Fire with your right hand!
Just give it up, mister!
Get it through your moronic skull already!
You're powerless against me!
Go for the grass.
Now I get it.
Clever move.
If you withdraw Golden Wind's ability, the
grass turns back into ordinary car parts.
Meaning we can turn around and shoot
the pieces at you like shrapnel!
What?
Did it work?
No, not quite.
We should be alright for
the time being, though.
The good news is, you
bought us a little time.
Our primary objective at this point
is getting what we need and escaping.
You can be sure the bastard won't
fall for the same strategy twice.
So forget about him and go, Mista!
I'll crack that lion open like
a pinata and find the disc.
I'll snatch it up and get out of sight.
All I need is a few seconds.
But will hiding be enough to
fool that winter wonder freak?
There's a good chance that plan will work.
But what if it doesn't?
All I know for sure is this
guy isn't messing around.
I don't want to think
about what'll happen if
he catches up with
Bucciarati and the others.
This deranged bastard needs to die!
And there's no time, like now!
What the?
Mista, what are you doing?
I'll prove you're not as
invincible as you think you are.
When you're forced to cover yourself
head-to-toe in ice, how exactly do you breathe?
There, I'm sure of it.
I hear the hiss of air coming
from the back of his neck.
So that's how he's breathing.
Numbers one and two get into
position to flank this strunzel.
And the rest, get ready to fly.
That nut job's looking here.
Watch out, he's gonna do
that ice thingy again.
No, the first thing on his
mind will be coming up for air.
Once he surfaces, I'll blast
that blowhole with some bullets.
Ready or not, here he comes.
Let's go, six bullets.
We strike the moment he takes a breath.
Mista, numbers one and two are reporting
that they can't find the breathing hole.
It's how he's positioned!
His head's angled up!
The opening's covered!
Shit, this plan's a non-starter!
Let's retrieve! Pipe down!
Break position and you
can forget about treats!
You got that one and two?
You got some balls attacking
my forehead like that! Meester!
What the hell?
You were trying to shoot the fish?
What stupid idea are you concocting?
Yes, he looked down! There it is!
All right, blast away!
Look sharp, we're gonna kill this!
One and done, it's time to run!
Huh?
Hold on, what's that sound?
What?
Don't tell me he's...
So, you figured out how I was
breathing and aim for that, eh?
Mista?
I told you, didn't I?
Sub-zero temperatures bring
everything in the area to a halt.
Gases become liquids and
liquids become solids.
Look a little closer.
See the suspended vapor now?
It's a bullet, Mista! That sound!
It was a ricocheting bullet!
Get out of the way! What?
That's White Ice's ability.
It's called Gently Weeps.
I'd already created a
frozen barrier of vapor.
Sure, it takes a lot of
energy to make it work,
but it protects me from
just about anything?
including your damn bolts and bullets.
I'm protected by a barrier of stasis.
I have you to thank for
that little trick, Mista.
Jonah's prediction was right on.
This is my fault.
Endless charge.
Why didn't I go after that
stupid disc from the beginning?
It's not on your benches or in the trash.
I know it wouldn't be in plain sight,
but there's nothing around here
that even resembles a disc.
Considering how eager
Mista was to get over here,
I'm sure the hiding spot
must be pretty close by.
Where is it?
The picture should give me a clue.
Things just went from bad to worse.
Mista's at the end of his rope.
He's taking responsibility for
this and is risking his life.
But that's just the mindset needed
to light your path in this darkness.
This is when things get interesting.
I've no doubt there will be sacrifices,
but Masa and I have determinazione.
We will find a way.
What the actual hell?
They stuck the thing in here?
In a crevice of a statue?
Damn it, I'm at point blank range.
From right here, I should be able to
take out his breathing vent and more.
If I can get close enough
to bypass his barrier.
This is bad.
Mista is desperate.
This whole ordeal, he's prepared
to pay for it with his life.
But this isn't simple grit
in the face of desperation.
He's saving us with Determinazione.
It's not martyrdom.
It's our road to victory.
A computer disk?
Of course, that's what you dubious
bastards were after all along.
A clear path to the boss!
Now that I have this, the boss can
say goodbye to his secret identity!
All that's left now is to capture Trish.
But first, I gotta do away with you fools.
Bring it, chuckle schmuck!
I can't wait to put you
out of your misery! Mister!
What the hell do you think you're doing?
This is what it means
to have determination to
forge your path through
the darkness of light!
Guido Mista, arrested at 17
on allegations of murder.
Despite the extenuating
circumstances surrounding the case,
his self-defense plea was rejected and
he was sentenced to 30 years in prison.
I was actually happy before this.
Is this really happening?
Mista had always been able to see the bright
side of things, but for the first time,
he was truly scared.
Shit.
Get up, you're free to go.
Are you the one who did this? Yes.
I saw your story on the news, and
I believe it was self-defense.
Now, from what I've seen,
you're a top-notch gunman, and your
inner strength is even more formidable.
Besides, a guy like yourself wouldn't
last two years wasting away in prison.
That's why...
Why you pulled some strings on my behalf.
So let me guess, you're a mafioso?
Come on.
I know a great restaurante.
Looks like you're enjoying that.
You should try the bruschetta if
you still have some room in there.
Of course. Mi scusi. Si?
Bruschetta for him.
And the others too, I suppose.
Four bruschettas.
No, make it five.
I can't be the lone man out now, can I?
Coming up.
Now, getting back to what
I was saying... I'll do it.
I actually think we'd
make an awesome team.
That's why I'm agreeing to it.
But first, order me a Dallas, too.
Oh, and some Tarot alle fragole.
You really are an odd one, aren't you?
Must be fate.
Ha, could be worse.
I guess it all worked out.
Mista came to realize that each and every
person has their own unique destiny.
And while youth tends to
be a difficult period,
filled with seemingly endless setbacks,
in the end, one always travels down
the path they're destined to take.
There.
The path is plain as day.
I just have to follow
it to the finish line.
I found it, Giorno!
I see it there, through the darkness.
It's the path to victory!
It's like you idiots just
refuse to learn your lesson.
Or were you not listening when I told
you sub-zero temperatures freeze vapor?
But if I were to take a frozen mass of
vapor and stuff it in my soup to melt down,
then the vapor would return
to its original state.
And since that state's basically air,
I'm like a diver with a scuba tank.
I don't need a breathing vent to
take in oxygen. Huh? Look at the van!
The guy deflected all six of the bullets!
How are we supposed to beat this bastard?
But you have all that determination
going for you, right, Mista?
Say your goodbyes.
My determination is unwavering, Giorno.
If you hadn't given me yours, I
would have never discovered my path.
The enlightened path that led me to
shove myself with my own bullets.
What?
I can't see.
The blood's congealed to my visor.
Path through the murky
darkness wasn't going to reveal
itself by blasting through
that protective ice wall.
No, no.
The easier route was to splash
blood all over your ugly mug!
I can't get it off!
Hey, it's the metal pole from earlier!
Nista, your bullet must have reshaped it!
Shit, that hurts!
What's this feeling?
Something warm and wet is
trickling down my back!
A moment ago, you asked
if I had determinazione.
Well, I'm gonna show you what it's all
about, but you gotta do the same for me.
Let me see just how determined you are to
be shot into the proverbial
hell frozen over.
This bastard's still upright.
What's worse, he's trying
to shove me back even more.
This lunatic is gonna kill me.
Merida, I gotta hurry
and yank this thing out.
Stop it!
The bullet will come back!
You won't survive another blow!
I have no choice.
That's what it means to have resolve.
Now buckle up, bullets, and hold on tight!
It's not over till it's over!
White Ice gently weeps!
It's too much, Mista!
You're gonna pass out!
Think about what that means!
We'll fade away!
No, not yet!
I've still got some
fight left in this body!
I can still pull the trigger!
Yeah, we won!
That's the way you got him good!
You're wrong, you fools!
Fine, you may have determinazione,
but I've got even more, guido mister.
I have to say, you dole
out some major damage.
Kudos to you, amigo.
However, losing all that blood
was actually to my advantage.
I froze the blood you forced out of
me and created my own icy support.
It keeps that pesky spike from sinking
further into my neck, so I'm good to go.
You won't beat me that
easily, you understand?
Oh, by the way, did you forget?
You still have a final bullet in play.
That's now in your skull! I win!
There's no wound?
Mista.
Your determination.
It shines even brighter
than the morning sun.
It's showed us the way forward.
And it's put us on the
path toward tomorrow.
We've won because of you.
What the hell?
I'm finally starting to realize
something about this Giorno Giovanna.
He's a total rookie, but even so,
when he says something will happen,
it eventually comes to fruition.
My Determinazione was really Giorno's.
It flooded my being without
me even realizing it.
It's like he superseded
Bucciarati to become Cape,
like he was guiding my every move.
How the hell does he do that?
Guess it doesn't matter.
Not like obsessing over
it won't do any good.
Hey, Mista.
We did it, huh?
We got the disc.
All thanks to you.
Yeah, that's great.
But could you please heal me?
I'm dying.
I was only able to do all that because I
knew you could fix me up after the battle.
Come on, before I bite the
big one, heal me up already.
Right away.
But first, I should probably clarify.
Golden Wind doesn't really fix things.
It creates parts I can add to you,
so there'll be new body parts.
I'll imbue the bullets in you with life,
replacing your damaged
blood vessels and tissue.
Great, just get started, please.
Oh, and there's one more thing.
Since I'm not actually healing your body,
you're still gonna have
a bit of residual pain.
What the hell?
Do you have to be so rough, Giorno?
Take it easy, Ande.
I'm injured.
I already told you
there's nothing I can do.
Settle down and take it
like a mafioso. Besides,
there's about 18 more to go, and you'll
have to strip if you want this to work.
Bucciarati!
I'm picking up two people.
It doesn't look like there's anyone else.
Proceed with caution.
My guess is, you've
found Mista and Giorno.
I'm sure the lack of excitement
has them longing for our return.
Giorno!
There they are! Mista!
Stop doing it so hard!
I leave my damn clothes on!
It's too intense!
Narancia?
Did you find them?
Why?
No, but...
There's something in my eyes! Giorno!
It's so hard to see in
this early morning light.
I'll keep after it, though.
It's not so rough, damn it.
I don't give a damn about nothing else.
Freaking you is all I need!
I need your body.
Tonight you got my time.
Tonight you
won't be sad?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
You got my mind.
All I want to do is free.
You must not say.
Oh, tell me.
What must I do?
To show how much I'm going to free.
Yeah.
You must not say.
Tell me what you must not do.
Tell me what you must
not do. I'm freaking.
Risotto, you bastard.
So you're coming to Venice.
I'm sure Bucciarati and his
men will take care of you.
Come what may, peace is at hand.
Thank you.